Translated by Releska
In the world of love, it's a dream of love
Of course, it's always with you
Oh, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
It's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay, it's okay
I'm so happy that you're so happy
If I'm crying, I'm not happy
The time ofキリの笑顔繋がるね
With you, you, you, you, you, you, your hand, if I like to do it now
I can't take it long without the feeling of time
where I'm feeling so deep
Ah ah ah ah ah ah
Welcome home
Not for a while
They were shocked to see the information about the game
That they had into the world
That they had into the world of making a world of new things
This is not even right
And they can get back to the world of the first thing they can do
But they did not focus on anything
They did not focus on the day of the day of the first big news
And they slowly started thinking that they would love this world
By the way, what's going on?
All the water is put into a toilet and rejuvenated the toilet.
What!?
I'll give it to you!
That's an all-in-one man, isn't it?
Hey!
I can do nothing to everyone!
This is a mess from a vegetarian restaurant!
Good afternoon!
Hello, I'm Akita!
The meat is 3,000 yen.
I'll give it to everyone.
Hey!
There are so many of them here!
Vegetables are delicious.
Is this vegetable vegetable?
Yes, it is.
Why do I have to eat it?
It's okay.
I took it as a substitute.
I'll eat it with a tap.
I'm sure it's a good thing to eat.
Let's eat it quickly.
It's not good.
Let's eat it.
It's the first time to eat vegetables.
I'm looking forward to what kind of taste it is.
Yes, I can do it.
It's because it's salad.
Salad.
It's delicious.
It's a good thing to eat this.
Really?
It's a really good taste.
Please wait.
It's not here yet.
This is not a good time to eat.
What did you eat, Mukamukara?
Was not good to eat Mukamukara?
I don't believe in it.
There are many things to eat.
How do we eat this vegetables like today?
Ah…
You're still planning to eat it, uh…
Ah, I'm kidding, you're changing your mind!
You're eating it up until it's too long…
Yes…
Did you want to eat too much for my husband's birthday?
Ah, you're having a hard time!
I have a belly for you, so I'm gonna have a big one, too!
Yeah!
Yeah…
That vegetable has a lot of green onions that have a lot of green onions!
Then I'll have to eat all the vegetables, Mugamukka!
Here, open the mouth of Mugamukka.
Did you have a lot of gari-gari with miko-niko-dot?
Oh, it's delicious!
Here, Mugamukka, eat it!
Oh, that's right.
That's right!
Oh, there are a lot of big blue bellies on the back.
You can eat this, right?
Ah!
Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum!
You can't do anything like that, right?
What?
You can eat delicious food, right?
Yum! Yum!
If it's cooking, let's wait for us.
Yeah, yeah, let's try it deliciously.
If it's too much, I'll get a hand.
You can cook it, right?
It's not a big deal.
It's a big deal.
I can cook it even if I look at it.
I can cook it even if it's too much.
I'm looking forward to it.
But why are you still here?
It's because it's too much.
It's a little too much.
That's good, right?
Yum! Yum! Yum!
Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum! Yum!
Now, everyone is ready.
This is the hamburger of Bejibergiri.
It's the taste of Russia.
This is Bejibergiri's curry.
There are also 8 of them.
Look at this.
Bejibergiri's fried chicken.
Oh!
Bejibergiri spaghetti.
Bejibergiri's gratin.
Bejibergiri's omelette ball.
Wow!
It's so good!
I'm going to eat it!
Oh! Yum!
It's so good!
Everyone is going to eat it.
I'm going to eat it.
I'll give it to you earlier.
And I'll give it to you.
What's this?
Where's the rice rice?
I'll take it.
How is it possible?
Well done, Mocha, Mocha.
I'm going to eat the rice rice.
I'll take it.
I don't want to cry.
I just want to be happy.
I'm already happy.
I know.
I'm going to eat it.
I'll do it.
I'm going to eat you, you idiot!
Oh, no!
Hey, you're so busy.
Ah!
Ah, you've been so busy.
If you're so busy, you'll be so busy.
Well, well, I'm not going to eat anything that's too much for you.
But, if you don't eat it, it won't be as big as you think.
Well, I'm going to eat it deliciously.
I'm not going to eat it because it's too much for me.
I want you to eat it as much as you want.
Muka Muka, are you sure you've seen Ueba before?
What?
Why don't Ueba and Selori eat all of them?
Is it okay to have Selori with you?
Ueba is the only Ueba who wants to eat all of them.
Huh?
Ah, that's why I'm...
Muka Muka?
I'm sure I've seen Selori before!
But I'll show you how I'm doing right now.
If I eat Selori, Muka Muka will eat it all of a sudden.
Look at me.
Oh!
Delicious!
Ueba, that looks so gloomy.
Oh, really?
I'll make it a little bit more.
No way! I can't eat it!
You can't eat that much, either.
You can't eat it, either.
That's right!
Yeah!
If you eat it first, you can eat it with me and Shirori.
Let's go!
Let's eat it.
I see.
Do you want to become bigger?
No way!
You can't eat it with me, either.
Oh, it's not with me.
It's a bit different.
It's similar to the smell.
Let's eat it with me.
You can't eat it with me, either.
No way!
Is it something wrong?
Are you okay?
Wait, I'll eat water right away.
Now, let's eat this.
With me?
Wait, what's wrong with you?
What's wrong with you?
I got it.
Where did you go?
I'm afraid that I won't eat it.
I'll be back when I eat it.
I'm sorry.
I got it.
What's wrong with you?
What?
Did you eat it with me?
Why should I season way of the day?
I'll be back when I enjoy it.
Wait, what's wrong with you?
Don't you have any easier jobs than to come as an adult?
Hey!
What do you want me to do?
What stupid bastard.
Don't do it to me.
Are you here for your colonies or something?
Then, let's listen to the song we've been playing.
This is a real song.
It's not a comic song, baby.
If you think about it, you'll see the end of the story.
What's going on?
Wait! Wait!
It's not over yet!
I'm reminded of you.
Oh, I'm so happy to be here!
But, hey, hey, hey!
I'm so happy to be here!
I've been working on the face paint for a while now.
I feel like I've been riding a cow since I was a girl.
I don't know how to do that.
I'm sure there's a difference between the other clothes.
I'm sure there's a difference between the other clothes that I'm wearing.
Oh, we're done.
We're done.
Well, you've got no sense, so I'm going to give you a chance.
Oh, it's Muka Muka!
Muka Muka, you're cool, aren't you?
Muka Muka is laughing!
Yes, you are. I'm cool, aren't you?
What is it that the chicken's head is bad?
Muka Muka is laughing at me.
Huh?
No!
You're not going to be able to get away with the magic of the other two!
You're going to be able to get away with the magic of the other two!
Muka Muka!
Hey, wait a minute!
Muka Muka, you're doing a weird thing to me!
It's not normal!
It's been a long time since I ate this vegetable.
I see.
I'm going to teach you a lesson.
Hey, you're doing a weird thing!
We've been here for a while!
Huh?
Muka Muka, where are you going?
Calm down, calm down, calm down.
You're not going to be able to get away with the magic of the other two!
That's right!
I see!
I'm going to be able to get away with the magic of the other two!
Muka Muka!
Isn't that ok?
It's true!
I always do weird things like that and sometimes just sometimes just have a good feeling.
I always do weird things like that and sometimes just have a good feeling.
That's right!
We've become good friends all the time!
Hey, Gamuka.
Why don't you just say until you're about to get away.
Well, you're going to say that you're going to be able to get away with the magic of the other two!
Yes!
We're已經 getting away with Muka Muka!
I don't have anything bad to live on.
This face and this face are my family.
What's wrong with you?
I'm so pissed off.
Hey, I got it.
I had a bad feeling that I had to eat it before.
That's why I got it before.
Oh, I don't know the answer to that.
But I'm sure that's why I got it before.
I got it, right?
I didn't know I had to eat it before.
Five?
I'm looking for another way to get it.
Do you have to give me a cheap plate?
A cheap plate?
Yes, a cheap plate.
I can't live without this.
That's right.
What's wrong with you?
I can't live without this.
How can you live without this?
I could live without this.
I personally don't want you to live without that.
An uncertain world.
It's a dream of an artist.
What's wrong with me?
I was unable to live without that.
Don't you know that?
I don't know where this place is or on TV.
Everything's out!!!
It's not there now.
It'd be there?
I will do it!
What should I do?
I will do it more clearly!
It's like I lost something.
I see...
I've finally found a fireball, Moon Kamuke.
I'm wondering if he's still in the 5th grade.
What it was?
Drinking our innocent, stupid punk!
Yes, Khan-san.
You, you!
The next one is...
3,000,000!
I'm going to save you!
What?
We're going to go together!
Let's go!
Ah, ah, ah!
Ah, ah, ah, ah!
Ah, ah!
Ah, ah, ah!
Do you think you can run away from the game?
You can run away from your game!
Ah!
Who will be able to escape this?
Let's wait until everyone gets to their destination!
Oh no! What's wrong with you?
You're the best of all!
Come on, Koji!
You can't run away!
What should I do?
I'm not going to laugh like that when I'm like this.
I'm going to use people who really don't laugh.
But I'm not going to do anything.
Ah, wait.
I won't let you down from there!
It's like you're going to get out of here!
I'm going to get out of here!
Ah, the other one is eating the fish!
Hey!
Oh, it's a quick!
It's bisogna beat the battle stage!
Place the ship on the case!
It's just enough to jump around faster than anything else...
It's okay...
Gaww, are you gonna get out of here?
Oh, here!
Oh, I got it! I got it!
Stalk!
If you can eat this vegetables, you can eat it.
The vegetables that are left behind will come in.
I see.
But it's not over yet.
What? Did you eat it yet?
I ate it.
Where did you go?
Hey!
What should I do with those people?
Hey! Hey!
Who are you?
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
The vegetables that are left behind will come out.
If you don't want to eat vegetables, you can come back.
Let's eat the vegetables that are left behind.
Hey!
It's delicious.
Hey! Hey!
It's okay if you don't want to eat vegetables that are left behind.
It's okay if you don't want to eat anything else.
It's really good to eat it.
You can't eat it without eating it.
But if you eat it without eating it, you can eat it.
It's a promise.
Hey!
Hey! Hey!
What a beautiful thing!
Hey! Hey! Hey!
The End
Lettingる空のようにのに
L жеつもいるの
ときを越え
ここへ来ているへ
へ・・なんや
私たち
何も言わづけるじじゃあダン
ければすけ
but the supporting charm of stars is muốn
Bay bai bai bai ababi
Let's do it!
Let's go let's go let's go let's go
The birds get the pinch-thick
Hot Story lets the song go beats
I did it!
And we have come back at the same time!
Yo-yo-yo!
The 6000-year-old and the five of those who laugh at each other,
You look great, Lucua-san!
Come here, smile like ugly!
What?
Why still movies, people,
So expensive!
You'll become ugly!
Next time,עなたカシの昭点外
Let's be happy!